<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" standalone="yes" ?><!-- edited with XML Spy v4.2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Morgoth (Targem) -->
<resource>
	<string
		id="CITPH01_Counterattack_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CIT: «Counterattack»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy all armored vehicles and patrol boats of the Crimson Dawn at Kane's island|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Nisia|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Mouette”-class patrol boat with a MLRS|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 four “Mouette”-class patrol boats|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CD patrol boats and armored vehicles|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 morning, foggy| |The enemy took the strategically important island in southern part of Nisia. Deployment of enemy forces on this front poses a serious threat and besides providing a beachhead for the enemy it prevents our future operations in the Chamenos region. According to intelligence, the enemy deployed several armored vehicles and patrol boats with anti-aircraft capabilities there. Your main objective is to clear out the island of the Crimson Dawn's forces presence and retreat before their reinforcements arrive. Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. The strike force for the mission will consist of two standard “Mouette”-class patrol boats and three modernized “Mouette”-class patrol boats, including yours." />

	<string
		id="CITPH02_Guests_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CIT: «Uninvited guests»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy the enemy heavy fleet|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Chamenos|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Provence”, “Lyon”-class destroyer|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 “Egale”-class light cruiser, two “Lyon”-class destroyers|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CD battleships, cruiser and destroyers|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 yes|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 possible|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 day, clear| |Loss of control over the southern part of the archipelago prevents our operations near Crete island. Your current mission is first in a series of counteroffensive actions in the region to retake the entire archipelago. Your main objective is to destroy the enemy strike force heading to Ellinika island. The enemy can call in the air support. Our helicopters can come to your aid to take down the heavy warships only when the enemy destroyers are eliminated.|Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. The strike force for the mission will consist of a modernized “Egale”-class light cruiser and three “Lyon”-class destroyers, including yours. As soon as the signal about the elimination of enemy destroyers is received, a flight of “Condor” attack helicopters will arrive to help." />

	<string
		id="CITPH03_March_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CIT: «March»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy enemy cargo ships|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Iles-Neuve|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Arlette”, “Egale”-class light cruiser|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 two “Egale”-class light cruisers|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CD cruisers, destroyers, patrol boats and fortifications|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 possible|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 morning, clear| |Your main objective is to destroy three enemy cargo ships heading to Port Helena from America with a shipment of weapons. The enemy doesn't expect such a sudden attack and according to the convoy route plan, two of the escort ships are going to stop at the port of Santa Maria. This is precisely when we need to strike the convoy. Once the attack begins, the enemy will likely deploy the attack helicopters stationed nearby. Try not to get too close to Libre island, since this territory is very well-guarded and features multiple lines of coastal defense. Furthermore, the enemy may call in additional reinforcements to defend the island.|According to intelligence, at the time of our planned attack on the convoy, a group of enemy heavy cruisers should be heading to America. Try to finish the convoy off as soon as you can to avoid the encounter with them. Their elimination, however, would seriously cripple the defensive potential of the enemy in the region, allowing us to retake the initiative. Consider this option only if the main objective of the mission is completed and you have not suffered serious losses.|Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. The strike force for the mission will consist of three “Egale”-class light cruisers, including yours." />

	<string
		id="CITPH04_Routine_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CIT: «Routine»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy enemy cargo ships|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Mediterranean Sea|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Murene”-class torpedo boat|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 three “Murene”-class torpedo boats|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CD destroyers and patrol boats|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 night, clear| |Here's the combat mission for this one: destroy two enemy cargo ships heading to Arjen with an important cargo. Their escort group consists of two “Albedo”-class destroyers and five “Reaver”-class patrol boats. Most likely, the patrol boats will start heading back to port due to their low fuel capacity once the convoy reaches mark 1, indicated on your map. This is going to be the perfect opportunity for you to strike, since the destroyers that will be left to protect the merchant ships are unlikely to have any effective ways of dealing with our torpedo boats. Thus, you can focus your attention on the main objective. Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. The strike force for the mission will consist of four “Murene”-class torpedo boats, including yours. You will be leading the operation, other boats will stand by for a signal to attack. Your boat getting detected at any point will serve as such." />

	<string
		id="CDPH01_Garrison_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CD: «Garrison»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 escort cargo ships through hostile waters|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Nisia|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Abogado”, “Albedo”-class destroyer|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 two “Albedo”-class destroyers|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CIT cruisers, destroyers, patrol boats and fortifications|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 possible|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 night, cloudy| |Storm weather in the southern part of the archipelago forced us to adjust course of the merchant ships that transport critically important cargo. Your objective is to safely escort the cargo ships through the hostile waters. Since the route lies close to the fortified island of Psaradon, expect heavy resistance. It is highly possible that the enemy will engage aircraft the moment CIT coastal artillery is attacked. Besides that, according to intelligence, the CIT destroyer group had to retreat from the southern part of the archipelago due to bad weather, and there is a high chance of an encounter with them. You can act independently, following ahead of the convoy if necessary. Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. Convoy composition: two cargo ships, three “Albedo”-class destroyers, including yours." />

	<string
		id="CDPH02_Fortress_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CD: «Fortress»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy enemy fortifications on Milos island|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Chamenos|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Cataluna”, “Furia”-class heavy cruiser|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 none|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CIT cruiser, destroyer, patrol boats and fortifications|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 yes|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 possible|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 evening, clear| |After the suppression of Commonwealth's fleet and line of fortifications in the Chamenos, the initiative in the region belongs to us. Only one pocket of resistance in this part of the archipelago is left - enemy fortress on the island of Milos. The island is heavily fortified and has multiple lines of coastal artillery. A single surface-to-air battery is also deployed on the island, which poses a threat to our aircraft. Destroy it to receive the help of our helicopters.|You will operate on your own before the squadron of “Mosquito” helicopters arrives." />
	
	<string
		id="CDPH03_Armada_Briefing"
		value="@ff000000CD: «Armada»| |@ff000000Mission objectives:@ff404040 destroy enemy fleet near Attans island|@ff000000Combat zone:@ff404040 Atlantic Ocean|@ff000000Vehicle:@ff404040 “Zaragoza”, “Leviatan”-class battleship|@ff000000Friendlies:@ff404040 two “Albedo”-class destroyers, missile cruiser “Argumento”|@ff000000Enemy:@ff404040 CIT battleship, cruisers and destroyers|@ff000000Air support:@ff404040 no|@ff000000Enemy aircraft:@ff404040 possible|@ff000000Weather:@ff404040 day, clear| |CIT heavy fleet at Attans island is going to hinder our planned amphibious operation on this strategically important piece of land in the Atlantic Ocean. Your main objective is to destroy the enemy “Librium”-class battleship. For this mission the high command has deployed the newest missile cruiser “Argumento” which should be able to eliminate the target quite easily. All you have to do is protect the missile cruiser until it is able to score a hit on the enemy battleship with its anti-ship missiles. In a case of a loss of the missile cruiser you will have to deal with the battleship on your own. The enemy is sure to deploy the aircraft, so keep your eyes open. Possible enemy movements will be indicated on your map. The strike force for the mission will consist of two “Albedo”-class destroyers, missile cruiser “Argumento” and your “Leviatan”-class battleship." />
</resource>
